

Nikita Golovlev | Frontenddeveloper

Email: nikitagolovlev.design@gmail.com

TG: @n_golovlev

GitHub: NikitaWebApps

Work Experience

Frontend-developer

Mar 2023 — current | Pharmaceutical Cosmetic LLC

- Development of websites and web applications using JavaScript/TypeScript, Vue, and Nuxt
- · Responsive and cross-browser layout using CSS, Sass, Tailwind CSS
- UX/UI design of landing pages, online stores, and applications in Figma
- Writing custom themes for WordPress in PHP
- · Worked in team with PM, marketer, and SMM manager

UX/UI Designer

Feb 2023 — Apr 2023 | Project work

- Developed the landing page design for the SaaS product
- Designed and built an online store

Sound Designer

Sep 2017 — Feb 2023

Sound design for Television and Movies

Skills

Languages

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Sass
- BEM
- TailwindCSS
- Vue
- Nuxt
- Pinia
- Astro
- GSAP
- VS Code
- PHP
- Wordpress
- Laravel
- Git
- GitHub
- Figma
- A11ly
- Tilda

Education

Interface Designer

Jun 2022 — Feb 2023 | Yandex Practicum

Creative Audio Director (MA)

Apr 2020 — Jul 2021 | Fachochschule Dortmund

- English B2
- German B2

Sound designer

Sep 2012 — Jul 2017 | GITR

About

I am front-end developer working with Vue / Nuxt with expertise in UX/UI design.

In my work, I use a product-oriented approach and always start by understanding the task. I ask clarifying questions, and if I see that something can be improved, I suggest options. I constantly develop in my profession: I try new technologies, delve into documentation, follow experts on YouTube, and read Reddit. In my free time, I make hobby projects to learn Laravel and play drums.